digiads.com.au 2013-05-24

# DIGIADS Privacy Policy

DIGIADS.com.au provides the following privacy statement: 

This privacy policy does not apply to parties that may be linked or associated with our website. Those website owners are responsible for the privacy of the information they collect and should be contacted directly for details of their privacy policies. 

**What information does DIGIADS.com.au collect?**  
DIGIADS.com.au records information from persons who visit websites operated by DIGIADS.com.au and or create an online advertisement, complete online forms, complete surveys or send us emails. This information is collected for business purposes. The types of information we keep on record will depend on the advertisement that you create, or the type of form or survey you complete or the product or service you request. Generally we keep a record of the following types of information about you:

  * Information that you have provided which may identify you, such as your name, address and contact details which you enter in a form or survey on our website;
  * Information that you have provided in the form of feedback or email; and 
  * Your permission to use your personal information for marketing purposes or to send you special offers from time to time.

It is not compulsory for you to provide us with your personal information which we may have requested from you for us to perform a service for you, however, without the specified information, we may not be able to fulfil your request or provide you with the service you require. 

Cookies may be used to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. 

When you visit DIGIADS.com.au, the following information is recorded for statistical purposes:

  * Your IP address; 
  * The date and time of your visit to the site;
  * The pages accessed and documents downloaded;
  * The referring web page; and
  * If you contact us, the type of browser and operating system that you use

**Note:** No attempt will be made to identify individual users with their browsing activities, except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where the law enforcement agency may warrant to inspect the Internet log files. 

**Note:** Some information disclosed to DIGIADS.com.au is passed on to other organisations or individuals so that they can help with browser inquiries; details are described below. Other than what is described below, DIGIADS.com.au will not pass on or sell information that relates to, or can be used to identify any individuals. 

**How does DIGIADS.com.au use the information collected?**  
All information disclosed to DIGIADS.com.au may be accessed by authorised DIGIADS.com.au Staff who may access your information to fulfil your request. 

**Advertisers**

If you are an advertiser on www.DIGIADS.com.au your information is held confidentially in a secure (see security) database. Some of your information will be published in your advertisement, in accordance with your instructions and for the period during which your advertisement is active. Your information is only accessible for alterations by you in your capacity as advertiser or by approved DIGIADS.com.au staff. It is the advertiser's responsibility to ensure that their details on the DIGIADS.com.au website are current and correct. 

Security & Scam Alert: Do not provide your log in details to anyone in response to email or phone requests. Click here for more information. 

**Browsers**

**Privately Advertised Used Auto/Car Enquiries**  
If you have submitted your details to inquire about a privately advertised used car, the information may be accessed and reviewed by our authorised DIGIADS.com.au staff and is passed onto the advertiser of the vehicle. If you do not wish for your information to be passed on, please do not complete our online inquiry forms. 

**Licensed Dealers Advertised Autos/Cars**  
When completing an online form to inquire about a new or used car for sale from a licensed car dealership, the information provided may be accessed and reviewed by our authorised DIGIADS.com.au staff and may be passed on to the licensed car dealer or other parties, (i.e. used cars: the owner of the vehicle; new cars: the nearest dealer(s) or other parties to suit your needs). The information that you provide is given to the licensed dealer or other parties to allow them to contact you in relation to the supply of information, testing and sale of the vehicle. The licensed car dealer or other parties are required to follow their own privacy guidelines with your information once received from DIGIADS.com.au If you do not wish for your information to be passed on, please do not complete our online inquiry forms. 

DIGIADS.com.au may undertake a survey to determine your use and satisfaction in relation to your inquiry. 

**Finance and Insurance Enquiries**  
When you enquire about finance or insurance, you will be asked to submit certain information. This information may be accessed and reviewed by authorised DIGIADS.com.au staff and may in addition be passed onto finance or insurance professionals from a third party organisation. This process is designed to assist you in obtaining information and services related to finance, insurance and other products to suit your requirements. If you do not wish for your information to be used in this way, please do not complete our online Finance or Insurance enquiry forms. 

DIGIADS.com.au may undertake surveys to determine your use and satisfaction in relation to your inquiry. 

**Vehicle Inspections**  
When you enquire about Vehicle Inspections, you will be asked to submit certain information. This information may be accessed and reviewed by authorised DIGIADS.com.au staff and may in addition be passed onto a third party organisation so that they can assist with your enquiry. This process is designed to assist you in obtaining products or services to suit your requirements. If you do not wish for your information to be used in this way, please do not complete our online Vehicle Inspection forms. 

DIGIADS.com.au may undertake surveys to determine your use and satisfaction in relation to your inquiry. 

**Other Online Forms:**  
When completing online forms for: 

  * **News and special offers from DIGIADS.com.au** , you will be contacted by DIGIADS.com.au via email with newsletters and details of special offers as per your request. You can opt out from this service at any time by following the instructions included in the newsletter or special offers sent to you or by clicking on the contact us link at the bottom of this page.
  * **For Sale Alerts** , you will be contacted by DIGIADS.com.au via email updating you on the latest vehicles as per your request.
  * **Email a Friend** , the details of the vehicle selected will be forwarded to the email addresses you supply to DIGIADS.com.au.

All information received from browsers is stored in a secure (see security) format for DIGIADS.com.au's own use. 

If you send us an email we will use your personal information to respond to your request. 

**SMS/Text Messages**  
We do not purchase or sell lists of cell phone numbers. 

**Can I access my personal information that I have previously given to DIGIADS.com.au?**  
Yes you can. You can request access to all of your personal information held in the secure DIGIADS.com.au database. We endeavour to ensure your information is true and correct at all times. Upon request, we can make adjustments and update your details to reflect correct data.

To send a request, please click here. Your request will be processed within 7 working days, depending on the nature of the request. There is no fee to access this information. 

**Security**  
In addition to the above assurances, any information held by DIGIADS.com.au and related individuals is held secure in a manner designed to protect information from internal and external access by anyone other than specifically authorised DIGIADS.com.au staff. We understand the importance of security for our consumers. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect personal data such as credit card information and finance or insurance application information during transmission, and maintain other commercially reasonable precautions to protect information that we store or retain.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
DIGIADS.com.au offers consumers the convenience of online personalization by using cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. When this information is stored on your hard drive, our system is able to recognize your browser and in turn customize web page content for you.

Cookies cannot be used to retrieve data from your hard drive, obtain your email address or obtain sensitive information about you. When a cookie is set, your browser will check it for length, an expiration date, and where it originated. Only DIGIADS.com.au can access the cookies that we set. 

DIGIADS.com.au allows our ad service company to set cookies as well. These cookies can "recognize" a consumer by a Unique identifier assigned at the time of the first visit, and may be used to measure site and page visits and browser version number, and browsing activity. This information may be used to better serve and provide advertising content on future visits and web pages viewed during your browser sessions on our websites. These cookies cannot obtain private information like name, e-mail or other personal information, and are not shared with DIGIADS.com.au. 

We use a third party tracking service who sets cookies on our site to track visits, page views and click stream behavior. The third party tracking service reports this data to us in aggregate so we can better understand our users and to improve our site. This information is not tied to any individual user. 

If you prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers will explain how to disable cookies under the help portion of the toolbar or notify you when you receive a new cookie. However, if you choose to disallow cookies on your hard drive, our Web site will not be able to provide personalization services. 

We also place "web beacons" on the website on behalf of third parties. A web beacon is a small, transparent image placed at various sections of our site to monitor user traffic. The web beacon records the number of click-throughs to the page where it resides and collects users' IP addresses, time the page was viewed, type of browser used, and existence of cookies from a previous visit. However, the data collected by our web beacons are used only in aggregated form, with no associated identifying information, and DIGIADS.com.au does not tie IP addresses to individual users or disclose the IP addresses to any non-affiliated third party. Information collected by web beacons is used only by DIGIADS.com.au, its affiliates and authorized vendors. If you do not wish such information to be collected, you can choose to deactivate cookies on your browser. 

**Changes to the DIGIADS.com.au Privacy Statement**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically or contact us at the contact points at the base of this statement. 

We will try our best to answer any queries as quickly as possible.
